let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'What sport is described as "the beautiful game"?',
        answer: 'Football',
        options: [
             'Rugby',
             'Football',
             'Tennis', 
             'Golf'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: 'Jurgen Klopp began his managerial career at which German club?',
        answer: 'Mainz 05',
        options: [
             'Borussia Dortmund',
             'VFL Wolfsburg',
             'Bayern Munich', 
             'Mainz 05'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which country's rugby team call themselves the springboks?",
        answer: 'Australia',
        options: [
            'Wales',
            'South Africa',
            'Germany',
            'Australia'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: 'The Chicago Cubs and Boston Red Sox play which sport?',
        answer: 'Baseball',
        options: [
            'Basketball',
            'American Football',
            'Croquet',
            'Baseball'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who is the Premier League's all-time top scorer?",
        answer: 'Alan Shearer',
        options: [
            'Alan Shearer',
            'Wayne Rooney',
            'David Beckham',
            'Didier Dogba'
        ]
    },     
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "In which sport do teams compete to win the Stanley Cup?",
        answer: 'Ice Hockey (NHL)',
        options: [
            'Rugby',
             'Ice Hockey (NHL)',
             'Basketball (NBA)',
             'Golf'
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How many MMA fights has UFC star Conor McGregor lost during his career?",
        answer: 'Six',
        options: [
            'Six',
            'Ten', 
            'Zero', 
            'Three',
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Who has won more grand slam tennis titles: Serena Williams or Roger Federer?",
        answer: 'Serena Williams',
        options: [
            'Serena Williams',
            'Roger Federer'
        ]
    }, 
    {
    numb: 9,
        question: "The Los Angeles Lakers and New York Knicks play which sport?",
        answer: 'Basketball (NBA)',
        options: [
            'Baseball',
             'American Football (NFL)',
             'Ice Hockey (NHL)',
             'Basketball (NBA)'       
            ]
    }, 
    {
    numb: 10,
        question: "Who won more caps for England: Wayne Rooney or David Beckham?",
        answer: 'Wayne Rooney',
        options: [
            'David Beckham',
            'Wayne Rooney'
        ]
    }       
       
]